vindicarlo.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Vin DiCarlo

## Privacy Policy

This statement sets out the privacy practices and policies in relation to any information that you may share with us in any capacity.

In this statement, when we talk about “we” or “our”, we are referring to VinDicarlo.com, and its majority-owned or controlled subsidiaries.

VinDicarlo.com reserves the right to update this policy from time to time, on reasonable notice to you. Your continued use of any website or service covered by this policy after we have notified you of an amendment will constitute your agreement to the same.

**Table of Contents**

  * Personal Information
  * Anonymous Information
  * Sharing Personal Information
  * Third Party Relationships
  * Security
  * Contacting Us

**1\. Personal Information  
**VinDicarlo.com is an information service provider. We may collect information on customers & email recipients including names, addresses, telephone numbers and other personal data.

VinDicarlo.com will use your persona information to establish your account, to communicate with you, for invoicing and statistical analisis. We also keep data for ongoing record keeping, as required by law.

VinDicarlo.com will not release personal information about you without your permission, except:

  * a. as permitted in this Privacy Policy;
  * b. as permitted in any written agreement between you and VinDicarlo.com;
  * c. where we believe it is reasonably necessary to conduct business; and
  * d. where we believe it is necessary to enforce our rights under any Agreement between you and VinDicarlo.com.
  * e. where we are legally obliged or ordered to do so.

VinDicarlo.com will provide a means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided to us, and a means for you to communicate your privacy questions and concerns to us.

We will not knowingly collect Personal Information on users under the age of eighteen. We encourage parents and guardians to monitor the Internet-based activities of their children.

**2\. Anonymous Information  
**“Anonymous Information” is information other than Personal Information, and includes the domain names, IP addresses and type of browsers that you may use, from time to time, referring URLs, and other, non-personally identifiable information.

When you access any site or service covered by this Privacy Policy, we collect Anonymous Information. We use this information for system administration, to market research (which is shared with partners), to personalize your experience, to show you more relevant content, and, generally, to improve our services. We share this Anonymous Information with selected partners in order to deliver relevant content.

VinDicarlo.com will not share any Anonymous Information if that information is or will be linked to your Personal Information, unless we have given you notice as described above and you have given us authorization to do so.

VinDicarlo.com can and will use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance, or to protect our service, site, or other users.

**3\. Sharing Personal Information  
**We will generally not share your Personal Information unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and you have authorized us to do so. Our partners who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people. In addition, if we add new features or services that might require the sharing of your personal information with other parties, we will provide you with notice and the opportunity to opt-in to receive these offers.

In certain special cases, we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with VinDicarlo.com’s rights, property or operations, other VinDicarlo.com users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

Finally, where, in our sole discretion after undertaking such investigation or investigations as we see fit, we determine that you have engaged in conduct which might be considered fraudulent or which might bring the reputation or standing of VinDicarlo.com into disrepute either with the general public or with a client or potential client of VinDicarlo.com, we reserve the right to release your Personal Information to such persons or third parties as we consider necessary in order to prevent you from causing injury to, or otherwise injuring or interfering, now or in the future, with VinDicarlo.com’s rights, property or operations or otherwise the rights, property or operations of anyone else who could be harmed by such conduct.

**4\. Third Party Relationships**  
VinDicarlo.com has relationships with many of the best media and services companies throughout the world.

Whenever you provide registration information on certain Web pages or for certain services provided in conjunction with third party partners, some data you provide is shared with partners. You should make every effort to read the privacy policies provided by or in association with such third parties, and make an informed decision on your own whether or not to continue utilizing the services based on the privacy policies posted on these co-branded Web pages, at your own discretion.

In addition to finding co-branded Web pages, you may find direct links to VinDicarlo.com on third party websites. You may also find direct links from third party websites to VinDicarlo.com. VinDicarlo.com cannot guarantee that these sites have adopted acceptable privacy policies. You should read these third party privacy policies, and make an informed decision on your own as to whether or not to continue based on these sites’ privacy practices, at your own discretion. No third party sites are covered by this Privacy Policy.

**5\. Security  
**VinDicarlo.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. VinDicarlo.com has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Unfortunately, no method of data transmission or storage is entirely secure, and while we make reasonable efforts to protect data stored on our networks, we cannot ensure or warrant that security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on VinDicarlo.com employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort (such as the use of employee passwords and non-disclosure agreements) to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

**6\. Contacting Us  
**If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, please contact: privacy@vindicarlo.com

**VINDICARLO.COM RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME. ALL CHANGES WILL BE POSTED TO THIS PAGE. WE WILL USE COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE EFFORTS TO NOTIFY YOU OF ANY MATERIAL CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**
